♪ ♪
[boy whimpering]
You wouldn't believe
the faces people make
when I just try to talk.
Well, they're gonna see.
[whispers] They'll see.
I'm gonna make them care.
They'll see the real me.
[whimpering]
God.
This loneliness is killing me.
Are you lonely too?
[whimpering]
[sighs, clears throat]
[on phone] God!
This loneliness is killing me.
-[popping lips]
-[on phone] God!
This loneliness
is killing me.
God.
This loneliness
is killing me.
God.
-This loneliness is killing me.
-[door opens]
Balthazar, get off the phone!
There's someone important
I want you to meet.
I'm busy.
Well, the internet will still be
here when you get back.
Come on.
[classical music playing]
[laughter]
Balthazar.
I'd like you to meet
Representative Hakeem Atkins,
the next senator
of the state of New York.
Balthazar.
Balthy.
Balthy?
That sounds like
a boy's name to me.
He looks like a man, Nicole.
[both laugh]
[Hakeem] Nicole, coming
to DC this weekend, right?
Oh. [chuckles]
I didn't know I was invited.
[Hakeem]
I need you by my side, Nicole.
It's my birthday this weekend.
Oh, well,
I'll let you two sort that out.
I know, I know, it's okay.
We'll talk to Antony.
Antony, my life coach?
-Fuck him.
-[whispers] He's right there.
Everyone has to grow up
eventually.
Balthazar.
[sighs]
[Balthazar exhales sharply]
♪ ♪
[panting]
[alarm blaring in distance]
[grunts]
Bang, bang! Bang, bang, bang!
Bang, bang, bang!
You're supposed to barricade
the door, guys.
Come on!
Now you're all dead.
[man] Right now you're probably
asking yourselves
who the heck we are.
Well, I'll tell you who we are.
We are Act On.
The global leader
in mass shooting
preparedness training.
And do you know who you are?
And it breaks my heart
every time I say this.
You are,
statistically-speaking,
the number one target
for mass shooters.
You know, real-life versions
of the simulation
that you're taking part in
happen every day.
Just last week in Arkansas,
where the perpetrator
didn't just have guns
and say they were planning
an attack,
they had drawn out maps
indicating entry
and exit points,
none of which was enough
for the authorities
to stop the shooting
before it happened.
Which goes to show
you are the last defense
in a mass shooting.
Let me ask you a question.
Who would you tell
if a student said
they had a gun and they were
planning an attack?
You.
Probably Ryan.
[Gore] Ryan?
My family's chief of staff.
Okay, but then he would tell
the principal, right?
Uh...
He'd probably reach out
to Len first.
Who's Len?
-My family's chief counsel.
-[chuckles]
Right.
You know, at Act On,
we study mass shootings
all over the world.
And whether it's high schools
or churches
or malls or movie theaters
or parades,
really any public gathering--
Yeah, you.
You said,
"all over the world"?
Yes. Act On is the number one
consultancy firm
for mass shooting
intelligence--
[student] Um...
But this doesn't happen
anywhere else in the world.
It's only in America where we
have such easy access to guns,
coinciding with
a zero-sum economy
and the monetization
of narcissism,
all of which push hopeless,
lonely people, kids,
into an annihilation mentality.
[student 2] Yo, what?
[laughter]
[Gore] That sounds like more
of a comment than a question.
♪ ♪
[no audible dialogue]
Here you go, Eleanor.
You're going to be
one of our victims today.
This stuff comes out
in the wash, right?
Okay. You probably think
everyone here is über-wealthy,
but I'm on scholarship, so...
Excuse me.
Can I be a victim too?
Uh... Whatever.
♪ ♪
[alarm blaring]
[indistinct chattering]
[girl screaming in distance]
[groans]
♪ ♪
[whispering] Hey, psst.
You okay?
What? Yeah.
It was a joke.
[laughs]
I love jokes.
I thought what you said
earlier was really cool.
Super different.
[Eleanor] Thanks.
It's pretty obvious,
though, right?
Talk to each other
in real life.
Be actual IRL friends.
Contribute to social good.
Why do all that
when you can just create
some douchebag company
that gets paid
to pretend terrorize us?
We're just like chasing
the violence we create,
you know?
Yeah, no.
Totally.
If you're really interested,
I'm hosting a rally tomorrow
in Washington Square Park.
You should come.
Yeah. Yeah, absolutely. I will.
And I'm super interested.
Hey, you guys,
you're supposed to be dead.
Anybody taking this seriously?
♪ ♪
[man] What you just heard
was a chilling account
of what happened inside
the Arkansas City shooting...
Hey Esteban,
Why do you think people
shoot kids in schools?
Huh? Um...
That's not something you have
to worry about, Balthy.
[Nicole] Yes, Hakeem
is very charming, isn't he?
[chuckles]
So, going into this next cycle,
how much do you think
you and Walter can give?
[Balthazar] "'We're fighting
for our lives here,'
exclaimed 19-year-old
James Howe."
"We're f--We--We're--
We're fighting for our lives."
"We're fighting for our--
for our lives here."
[voice breaking]
"We're fighting for our lives."
"We're fighting
for our lives here."
♪ ♪
I just saw the news
about Arkansas City.
No, you're not there yet.
Try again. Try again.
This awful country's just...
[voice breaking]
chasing the violence it creates.
It's not fair!
[exhales sharply, sniffs]
One more time.
I just heard the news
about Arkansas City.
[sobs]
Just give us IRL friends.
We're fighting
for our lives here.
I wanted to be honest
with you guys.
And what do I fucking get?!
Nothing!
I don't know
what the fuck I'm doing.
That fucking shoot--
Did you only touch me
'cause I was little?
Why did you rape me?
You're a fucking pedo!
♪ ♪
[Deathdealer16]
Cry about this, pussy.
This shit is all
I think about every day.
[Balthazar]
Are you lonely?
[Deathdealer16]
Of course I'm lonely.
I'm a fucking school shooter.
[Balthazar]
For real?
[Deathdealer16] Want to see
what I'm gonna do?
That's the Arkansas City
shooting.
This is the shit
they won't show on the news.
[gunfire]
[people screaming]
[car horn honks]
[Balthazar]
Hey Esteban,
do you like Hakeem?
I'm not big into politics,
Balthy.
Why not?
If you ask me,
it's a big grift.
What's a grift?
A con.
Thieving. They make you
care about something,
they take
your hard-earned money
and don't do nothing with it.
It's a grift.
[indistinct chatter]
Eleanor.
Eleanor. Hey.
-[man] Bye.
-Bye.
What happened,
where's the protest?
Oh, um,
only ten people showed up.
Are you kidding me?
I mean, come on!
We're fighting
for our lives here.
Yeah, I know.
♪ ♪
Well, what are you doing now?
[Eleanor] So this is what
a $50 million view looks like.
Holy shit. Is that the Met?
[Balthazar]
We have an indoor pool too.
Not much of a swimmer, though.
My life coach
uses it sometimes.
-Your life coach?
-[Balthazar] Yeah.
He was brought in
a couple years ago
to help me
"break out of my shell."
I haven't seen him much since
he started his new company.
Not that I need him.
What about your dad?
He lives in Westchester,
with his other family.
[chuckles]
But he pays
for everything, so...
Can I show you something
in my room?
Okay.
[Balthazar on phone]
This awful country is just
chasing the violence
it creates.
Just give us IRL friends.
We're fighting
for our lives here.
Is this sincere?
Are you actually crying?
Uh, that's a good question.
Um, I think it's nice
to be a part of a community.
Yeah, like, you and activism.
Ooh, ooh, ooh. Check this out.
I started DMing with a guy
that commented on it.
And you're gonna like this.
Look at what he sent me.
Why would I like that?
Because he's a school shooter.
He needs our help, Eleanor.
We could--we could stop
a school shooting.
Okay, let me show you
this other thing he sent me.
Security footage.
From the one in Arkansas.
[people screaming]
[gunshot]
[gunshots]
[screams]
What are you doing?
Are you fucking psycho?
Wait. What?
-[Eleanor] Jesus.
-I'm sorry, Eleanor,
[stammers]
it's just a video, though.
I thought
that's what you're into.
It's not just a video.
It's death.
-It's real death.
-Yeah, I know that--
It's really obvious none of
this actually matters to you.
You're just pretending it does.
-I'm not. I'm not.
-How the fuck
-do I get out of here?
-No. I'm not.
I'm not pretending. I care.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
It's my birthday this weekend.
So?
Jesus Christ, you really are
-a fucking psycho.
-[elevator dings]
It's really obvious none of
this actually matters to you.
None of this
actually matters to you.
It's death. It's death!
It's really obvious.
None of this
actually matters to you.
It's real death.
You are just pretending
it does.
What the fuck?
[Eleanor]
You're just pretending it does.
You're a fucking psycho.
It's really fucking obvious
none of this
actually matters to you.
You're just pretending.
It's really obvious
none of this
actually matters to you.
♪ ♪
[Balthazar]
Hey, Death.
♪ ♪
[Deathdealer16]
Wassup, pussy?
[Balthazar]
Having kind of a bad day.
My girlfriend called me
a psycho.
[Deathdealer16]
That's every day for me.
Except no girlfriend.
That's why I want to kill
everyone and everything.
[Balthazar]
Don't do it.
I really want to help you.
No.
Are you there?
Don't do it!
What the fuck?
♪ ♪
[Balthazar]
Saw your profile.
What do you think of this?
[Deathdealer16]
That's very forward.
Is this a scam?
[Balthazar]
Not a scam.
You seem like my type.
[Deathdealer16] Huh. Sick.
[Balthazar]
Where do you live?
[Deathdealer16] Why?
[Balthazar] Because I want
to be in your bed.
[Deathdealer16]
It's been a long time
since I had a warm body
cuddled up against me.
[Balthazar] You know
what else I want to do?
[Deathdealer16 chuckles] What?
LOL.
I knew you were all talk.
[Balthazar] Keep your cock
as deep in my throat
as it can go until
your balls have pumped out
every last drop of cum.
[Deathdealer16]
Damn.
That's cool.
But honestly, I just want
to hear your voice.
So I know you're a real person.
[Nicole] Ahh, I see.
Well... [continues indistinctly]
Mom?
Oh. Balthazar,
I didn't know you were awake.
Oh, honey,
did you get any sleep at all
last night?
Please don't go
for my birthday.
Oh, Balthazar.
[phone chimes]
Why didn't you tell me about
the shooter drill at school?
I want you to know that me
and some other parents,
we have already started
a petition
to stop companies like that
from operating
in Manhattan schools.
Uh, is that all you're doing?
Oh, well, I guess,
I could talk to our lawyer,
or... I know what.
I'm going to bring it up
with Hakeem.
He can talk to people
in Washington
-on your behalf.
-[phone chimes]
-And you--
-Okay, Mom. Bye, thank you.
Have a nice trip.
[Nicole]
Bye. Happy birthday.
[AI Nicole] I want to lick
the shit off your dick
after you fuck my ass.
[Balthazar] Do you want
to meet in real life?
♪ ♪
Hey, guys.
Something very important
happened to me last night.
I couldn't cry.
And you know, if you know me,
you know that crying
is the only way I feel real.
But recently,
someone I care about
told me that my crying
is insincere.
So I guess it's not real.
[whispering] Do you want to come
to Texas with me?
We can do this.
See, I've been talking
more to that guy.
[Balthazar] See, but it's
confusing because--
I'm not crazy, okay.
...some people say
they want you to be sincere.
But then when you show them
how sincere you are
by inviting them to Texas
to try to change
the world with you,
-they freak out.
-[inaudible dialogue]
And--and--and make
a huge scene in the hallway
because they care more about
their stupid scholarship
than they do
about kids getting shot.
Everything okay?
[Balthazar] Well, I don't have
a stupid scholarship.
Fine. Fine.
-And maybe the shooter--
-Hey!
[Balthazar] ...is expecting
a different person.
I'm the one who cares, Eleanor!
Me, I do.
But once he gets to know
the real me,
we'll become friends.
And then
I'll tell him the truth
and he'll understand.
Because, guys,
if you really care,
you have to show up.
I'm showing up.
Are you?
Yeehaw.
[man 1]
What's his name again?
[Antony]
Balthazar. It's his birthday.
Yo, surprise!
-[man 2] Surprise!
-[cheers]
[Antony]
Happy birthday, buddy.
Hey, where are you going,
buddy?
You're gonna miss your party.
[sighs] It's not my birthday
till Friday, Antony.
Yeah, I know.
Hey, listen, I'm sorry.
Friday's really busy for me
and my other clients.
Your mother said
you don't have any plans.
Wait. What are you
all packed up for?
-Whoa. Hey.
-Just let me--
Balthy, you know I still
submit reports to your father.
Okay, so then submit
your stupid little report
and tell Robert that I'm fine.
You need his money just as bad
as Mom does, don't you?
Okay. All right. Listen.
Who the fuck are these idiots?
Who are these people?
Hey, hey, it's Chris,
Devon, Rebecca.
You know John. That's John.
John from Safe Landing.
-[Balthazar, mocking] John. Oh!
-How about this?
How about you just tell me
where you're going?
What would that do
for the kids, huh?
Kids? What do you mean, kids?
The kids. The kids, Antony!
Balthazar, Balthazar.
You're coming off
really manic right now.
I know why I haven't seen you
as much this past year.
It's not because
of all your new clients.
It's because... [sniffles]
You're not attracted to me
anymore, isn't it?
Is it because I hit puberty?
Shut that shit down.
Stop that shit right now.
Did you only touch me
'cause I was little?
Bro, I've seen your videos.
I've seen them. Stop it!
He's doing a bit.
It's not funny.
-Why did you do this to me?
-Stop!
Why did you do this to me?
Why did you?
[sobbing]
Why did you rape me?
Balthaza--
You can't say shit like that.
-Hey, stop!
-[sobbing]
-Why did you do--
-Bro.
-I won't tell anybody!
-Stop it.
-Just let me go please.
-There's nothing to tell.
There's nothing to tell.
There's absolutely nothing--
Yeah, right. Yeah, right.
-You're a fucking pedo!
-Shut the fuck up!
Antony! Let him go!
You need to calm down.
-What in the fuck?
-Relax. He's a kid.
[woman on PA]
Your attention, please.
Passengers are allowed only...
[tone plays]
[indistinct PA announcement]
♪ ♪
-[Supes] I am ready for war!
-[crowd] War!
-Whoo! Whoo!
-[crowd cheering, applauding]
Holy shit.
I think I see a room
full of fucking winners.
[crowd cheers]
Y'all wanna know something
about winning?
[scattered shouts]
In order to know how to win,
in order to get to the top,
y'all gotta get to know
the bottom.
-[man 1] That's right.
-[man 2] Yes, sir.
Lock that in, folks.
Suffering builds winning.
Say it with me now.
[crowd]
Suffering builds winning!
That's right.
That's why
our keynote's here today.
When I first met him,
he was fresh
out of the penitentiary.
Not a dime to his name.
But you know
what I saw in his eyes?
♪ ♪
This motherfucker
wanted to win.
[crowd cheers]
Let's show some love
for the one and only...
Beaver fucking Jackson!
[crowd cheers]
[upbeat rock music playing]
[crowd chanting] Beaver! Beaver!
Beaver! Beaver!
Yeah!
[laughs]
Hey, can we, uh--
can we turn
all that noise off, please?
-[music stops]
-Thank you.
The Beaver Jackson
that you see standing here
in front of you today
is a fucking winner.
[scattered cheers]
[stammers] I'm not going to talk
about today.
I'm talking
about seven years ago.
[exhales sharply]
Seven years ago,
I was dried up,
broke, busted, beaten.
I was an addict.
Mostly sex, but meth too.
I walked out on my family.
My wife, God rest her soul.
My 13-year-old boy.
And I looked everywhere
for someone else to blame,
except...
-[crowd] The source!
-Source!
For nearly a decade,
I didn't see my boy.
My...
[chuckles]
My beautiful boy.
I was a bad father,
like I imagine
a lot of you are.
And then
one day...
-Thrush.
-[crowd cheers]
Incredible crowd today.
I'm telling you
that personal shit sells.
All right.
Do I have to sell all this
before I start making anything?
Are you whining?
-No.
-Jesus, Solomon.
-I'm not.
-I got Supes to get you
the wholesale rate,
-and you are whining.
-I'm not whining.
I just didn't think
it was gonna be that much.
You got that money or what?
[sighs]
Yeah. Hey. All right.
Move this supply,
you've made your money back.
Sell any more?
Just fill out this slip.
Send it to the home office.
That's as good as money.
And remember,
you sell the story,
not the product. Understand?
Yeah. Sell--sell the story,
not the product.
Hey, Dad.
You know, I reached out
to you 'cause...
I know we haven't spoken
in a few years,
but I've been...
I've been having a hard time.
-There you go.
-I thought we could...
[horn honks]
Supes!
You want to talk
about a hard time?
You hear about that
shooting up in Arkansas City?
No.
[Beaver] His little cousin
got shot there.
You don't hear him whining.
Okay, Sol, I gotta boogie.
Congrats, kid.
Welcome to the Thrush family.
-Thank you.
-This'll be good.
For us, for uh,
for our relationship.
Come here, kid.
[chuckles]
[tires squeal]
[J-metal music playing]
[singers singing in Japanese]
-[music stops]
-'Sup, Carson.
Hi, Grandma.
-Grandma?
-[Elaine] Hey, baby.
-I'm back here.
-All right.
Gonna need a little help.
[Solomon] You gotta stop
going to the bathroom
-without your walker.
-I know.
I know, I know, I know.
I thought I could do it.
I need your help getting up.
-I got you.
-[grunts]
-[Solomon] You all right?
-[Elaine] Yeah.
-Oh, God.
-[Solomon] Come back.
[Elaine] Yeah, yeah.
Okay, here we go.
-[Solomon] Let's do the dance.
-[Elaine laughs]
It's like a conga line.
[both laugh]
[Elaine] I was doing good,
and then it just got aggravated.
You know what I mean?
All right,
all right, all right.
God bless.
Hey, guess what?
What?
You're looking at...
the future number one
supplement salesman
in North Texas.
A salesman?
How about that?
Fuckin' A, baby.
Hey, can I practice
my pitch on you?
Shit. If I weren't your grandma,
and you showed up at the door,
try more than a pitch on me.
[chuckles]
-Grandma.
-[Elaine chuckles]
-All right.
-[Elaine] Ha!
♪ ♪
[knocking]
My name is Solomon Jackson,
and I'm Thrush
independent advisor.
-Thrush?
-That's right.
Can I ask you all
to do me a favor?
All put your hands up
and take a close look
at your fingers.
You see this finger here?
It's your index finger.
You see this one next to it?
You see how they are similar
in length?
Well, that means
you are short on testosterone.
-What is that?
-[Solomon] It's in your balls.
-In your peepee.
-Oh, really?
And I know you love your mama.
She did not expose you
to enough testosterone
in the womb.
-I'm afraid she bore you weak.
-Solomon.
[Solomon]
At this stage in your life--
Maybe not this stage, but--
Grandma!
You listening?
-You fell asleep.
-[Elaine] Oh, shit.
Well, you can put
your hand down.
Done that bit.
Are you ready for war?
Because you're going to need
as much war fuel testosterone
that a body can take.
-Git!
-[man] Get the fuck out of here.
-[man 2] Fucking git.
-[woman] Good night, Solly.
I'm sorry.
Ooh! Oh, Solly,
that was so fucking good.
Hey, you're keeping your job
at the Pump-N-Go, though, right?
Yeah, yeah.
I just want to find a way
that I can show up
for myself a bit more.
Your mama
would be so proud of you.
Thanks, Grandma.
♪ ♪
[no audio from phone]
[whimpering]
News just broke
about Arkansas City.
You hear the news, Solly?
You better sell
more of those dick pills
or you're going to be living
underneath the bridge
with the bums.
Rent went up 65 percent.
65?
What the fuck
am I supposed to do, Myron?
How are we supposed
to pay that?
Hey, don't shoot
the messenger, buddy.
I'm not shooting--
Yeah, I fucking
will shoot somebody.
Blow someone's
fucking head off.
-Hey, fuck you.
-Fuck you, old man.
Fuck you, you little prick.
[J-metal music playing]
[horn honks]
♪ ♪
[electronic doorbell plays]
Taylor.
Hey, now, stop me
if I'm getting
out of line here, Brian.
But I'm assuming
you don't want to be
assistant manager here
your whole life.
Shitty ass office doing
schedules the whole time.
Don't you want something more?
Don't you want to feel
like a real man?
Dude, you called in 30 minutes
before your shift started
yesterday.
I ended up having
to cover for you.
-No, but--
-Do you honestly believe
-that you still have a job here?
-No. My dad was in town.
He doesn't come around
very often.
That--that doesn't matter, man.
There have been complaints.
Now, I'm not saying who,
but you make your
female coworkers uncomfortable.
Taylor is the only female
that works here.
Taylor, why did you say
I made you feel uncomfortable?
-I didn't say that.
-Yes, you did say that.
-Brian just told me you did.
-Brian!
All I did was ask you to go
to the Jimmy Phantasm event
-at the Astrodome.
-Yeah.
And I said no,
because I'm an adult.
So saying no
makes you feel uncomfortable?
No, Solomon.
You asking me if I think
cartoon characters are hot
makes me uncomfortable.
You talking to me
about your dad's dick
-makes me uncomfortable.
-I can talk--
And you lingering around me
in the store,
struggling to make small talk
because all
you can think about
is cartoon characters
and your dad's dick--
-That's not--
-[Taylor] ...makes me
-fucking uncomfortable.
-That's not all I think about!
You're like
a fucking incel guy,
and that's uncomfortable.
I'm not an incel, Taylor.
I'm not a fucking inc--
You know what?
Fuck you, Taylor.
'Cause all I wanted
was for you to be my friend.
And now I'm gonna be
fucking homeless
because of it, you know that?
[Brian]
Solomon, it's time to go, man.
Solomon, get out of the store.
Go!
-Don't make me call the cops!
-[Solomon shouts]
Go, get out of the store, man.
Fuck you, Brian!
-[Brian] Go!
-[Taylor] Bye.
[electronic doorbell playing]
[heavy metal music playing]
[music continues]
[man] How are you doing today?
I got some guns
I'm trying to get rid of.
Sorry.
Unfortunately, there's no
serial numbers on these.
It's a federal crime
to buy these.
They're good guns.
They shoot straight.
Please stop touching the gun,
okay?
-No. My dad gave these to me.
-[man] I understand.
Your dad did you wrong.
I'm sorry.
I can give you a good deal
for these.
-I bet you would.
-What's that supposed to mean?
-You're not gonna take them?
-No, sir.
You know somewhere that might?
-No, sir. You have to leave.
-Okay.
Well, that's your loss.
These are good guns.
They have
a lot of sentimentality to me.
I don't buy sentimental stuff.
-Fuck you.
-[man] Fuck you, too.
[Solomon] Fuck!
♪ ♪
[whispering] You're the source.
You're the source.
-You're the source.
-[gun cocks]
[gun fires]
[dial tone ringing]
[Beaver]
This is Beaver Jackson,
senior consultant
at Thrush Inc.
Can't get to the phone
right now
but I look forward
to connecting with you.
Leave a message. All right.
[phone beeps]
Hi, Dad.
I...I know you told me
only to text you.
Please don't be mad.
I, I think--
I think I made a mistake.
Um...
We need that money
I gave you and...
[stammers] Can I give
some of this stuff back?
Just let me know.
[imitates gun firing]
[imitates gunshot]
♪ ♪
[crowd]
Solomon! Solomon!
[thunder rumbling]
[computer chiming]
♪ ♪
Yeah, right.
[computer chiming]
Oh, shit.
[AI Nicole] I want to lick
the shit off your dick
after you fuck my ass.
Yo.
♪ ♪
[woman over PA]
The 710 Express from Houston
is now arriving at bay nine.
Hey, you Terra?
Terra?
Fucking...
[Balthazar] Solomon?
Solomon. Right?
Do I know you?
Um, yeah. You're waiting
for a girl, right?
Terra? Is that right?
Who the fuck are you?
What is this?
[Balthazar] I met Terra
on the bus, and yeah,
she asked me
to come and find you
and tell you sorry. Um--
What do you mean, sorry?
She had to turn around
because her sister,
she's in the hospital.
The fuck are you talking about?
Why wouldn't she just
message me that herself?
-Because her phone broke.
-What is this?
-Is this a trick?
-No!
-Are you fucking with me?
-No, I promise!
-Is this a fucking trick?
-I swear, I swear.
Please don't hurt me.
I'm sorry.
You telling me the truth?
Yes.
This is the truth?
Yes, I promise.
-Fucking stupid.
-[Balthazar] No, no, no, no.
-So fucking--
-No, no, no, no. It's okay.
She's going to text you
as soon as her phone
starts working.
She said that?
Yeah, yeah.
And she was...
she was really looking forward
to meeting you.
♪ ♪
I can't believe I thought
it was a fucking trick
when her--when her sister
might be dead.
I'm such a piece of shit.
Fucking--fucking piece of shit.
-I fucking hate my brain.
-[phone dings]
[singer singing in Japanese]
[Solomon]
Who are you texting?
It's just my mom.
She wants me to call her back.
Do you like your mom?
Uh-huh. Yeah.
Well, then you call her
right now.
All right? You never know
what you got till it's gone.
Fucking call her right now.
I'm serious.
[dial tone ringing]
[Nicole] Balthy?
-Balthy, hello?
-Yeah. Mom! I'm here.
[Nicole]
Oh, I'm so glad you called.
How was your birthday
with Antony?
Yeah. It was fine.
His sober companion friends
came over,
-and they went swimming.
-[Nicole] Oh.
Antony said
he brought a cake, too.
Did you have
a really good time?
[AI Nicole] I want to lick
the shit off your dick
after you fuck my ass.
Fucking knew it.
[Balthazar laughs]
Okay, Mom, I gotta go. Gotta go!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Give me your phone.
My what?
[scoffs] My phone?
Fucking give it to me!
Okay. Okay.
Solomon. Calm down.
It's me.
Balthy!
BBoyMalone? We were messaging,
I'm from New York.
You remember that, right?
You remember, don't you?
Come on, man, you remember
we were messaging.
[grunting]
I just wanted to be friends!
God.
I just wanted
to be your friend.
to be your friend!
♪ ♪
-[Solomon] Hey.
-Oh.
What'd you say
about being my friend?
You looked like
you needed someone.
And you took a bus
to Fort Worth for that?
No. I flew
from New York to Houston,
and then I added a bus trip
because I didn't think
it'd be believable
if you picked Terra up
from an airport.
What, all that,
just to be my friend?
Well, get in!
So when were you planning
on doing it?
Doing what?
Um, school shooting.
School shooting?
Yeah. That's what you said.
That's why I'm here.
'Cause I thought that maybe...
I thought maybe
that if you had a IRL friend,
you wouldn't do it.
That's why you're here?
You think
I'm some kind of maniac?
Man, I should--
I should fucking smoke you.
-Smoke me?
-Dumb ass.
-With what, with a gun?
-Yeah, what the fuck you think?
Bitch! Open the glove box.
Huh?
Oh!
[Solomon]
Never seen one before?
IRL?
No.
You wait till you see
the rest of what I'm packing.
♪ ♪
[Solomon]
What you lookin' at?
Come on.
-Hey, Grandma.
-[Elaine] Hey, baby.
-You gonna shut the door?
-[Balthazar] Oh.
[Solomon] This is, uh...
It's my new friend.
♪ ♪
-What's your name again?
-Balthazar.
-Everyone calls me Balthy.
-It's Ballsy.
-[Balthazar] Balthy. Bal-tee.
-Ballsy?
No, it's Balthy.
-It's French.
-Okay, well, whatever.
Can you believe this cocksucker
came all the way
from New York to visit me?
-[laughs]
-[Solomon] Dumb ass.
Wait here.
You dragged your ass
all the way from New York City
to see my Solly?
Solly tell you
what's been happening
-around here?
-[Balthazar] Mm-mm.
They are raising the rent.
Motherfuckers.
♪ ♪
Yeah, we're going
to have to find
somewhere else
to live pretty soon.
Hmm. Yeah, that'll be nice.
You could buy a real house.
[Solomon]
Balthy! Come here.
-Whoa.
-This what you wanted to see?
Look at that.
"Love is forever
an elusive bird, stuck--"
[Solomon]
Not that.
That's the first plan
I ever drew up.
And that's where
it all started.
Yeah.
I had a lot of phases. [sniffs]
You like Jimmy Phantasm?
It's been with me
since I was a kid.
That's my guy right there.
♪ ♪
♪ Yo, Jimmy
was your average teen ♪
♪ A brainiac whiz
who invented a machine ♪
♪ To catch ghosts,
tracked them with EVP ♪
♪ And tap them
with a subatomic laser beam ♪
You guys are getting kicked out?
-What?
-Your grandma.
She said you guys
are getting kicked out.
No, off the land.
-It's our trailer.
-Oh.
Fuckers want to charge me
ten grand to move it.
Fuck them.
Is that a lot?
Yeah, but I'm going
to shoot them all
in their fucking faces.
[laughs and imitates gunfire]
[imitates gunfire, cackles]
♪ Go, go, go!
Jimmy Phantasm ♪
♪ Go, go, go, go! ♪
-You hear those babies crying?
-[gun firing]
[laughs] Well, not anymore.
They're dead.
Hey, you want to use
the, uh, pistola
or one of the ARs?
♪ ♪
Look. There's a few.
Hey, hold it like a fucking man.
Put it up. You got a grip?
I know you're going
to like it. Put it in.
Shoulder, here.
Hips, square them up.
Look down the scope.
Don't worry.
Safety's on.
It's not just going to go off.
See the bottles?
Hey, it feels good,
doesn't it?
Now remember,
don't ever point a gun
at someone
unless you mean to use it.
Okay?
These things kill people.
Yeah, I know that.
That's why I'm here.
Yeah. Me too.
[gun clicking]
Nothing happened.
-Safety's on, stupid.
-[safety clicks]
Shoot it.
Whoa. Whoa.
[gun firing]
Oh.
Oh, you like that shit,
don't you? [chuckles]
♪ ♪
Let me do it again.
-Yeah, but this one.
-[gun cocks]
-Same deal. Shoulder.
-Yeah.
Grip it, down the barrel.
[Solomon laughing]
Mmm, nice shooting, city boy.
Mmm.
Yeah. That hurts, doesn't it?
Hey, you know why yours hurts
and mine doesn't?
Because the bad news is, Balthy,
you were born-- hey!
[snaps fingers]
The bad news is
you were born a little bitch.
It's probably why you're sore
from all that kickback.
And it is definitely why
you make
all those crybaby videos.
But the good news
is that if you act fast,
you can take a look
in the mirror today
and take some responsibility
for that low T count.
Hey, let me ask you
a question, Balthazar.
Are you ready for war?
Because a war is coming,
and you gotta be able
to protect yourself
and your family.
Which is exactly what
a daily serving
of Thrush will do.
You trying to sell me these?
Yeah.
I don't think I'm interested.
[Solomon] I tell you.
Well, I could see myself
getting real angry, Balthy.
You know?
Just at the world,
like in Arkansas City.
16 people dead.
Just bam, bam, bam.
Okay. Okay.
[stammers]
If I buy these,
will you not do
a mass shooting?
Unfortunately, no.
But if you bought all this
and then put in an order for...
one year's supply...
well, then maybe.
Maybe I could see myself
standing down
for a bit.
Yes. Yes, yes.
Whoo-hoo! [grunts]
[whooping] Oh, yes!
Oh, my dad is gonna flip.
[laughing]
Yes! Yes!
[woman moaning]
[flesh slapping]
[Beaver]
Can't go wrong, baby.
-[woman] Oh my God.
-Can't go wrong, right, baby?
[Solomon laughs]
[Beaver]
You like that, baby?
Can't go wrong, baby.
[Beaver panting rhythmically]
That's your dad?
Uh-huh. Yeah, he did porn
a few years, amateur MMA.
He had a bit
of a dark phase with drugs.
That's how my mom died.
Now he's the biggest
Thrush distributor
in the region.
When he sees how much I sold,
I feel like he's going
to invite me in.
The inner circle.
We'll start making
real money together.
I've been meaning to ask,
you're not really crying
in those videos, right?
Mmm.
Well, I can make myself cry.
That doesn't mean
it's not real.
You think you could show me
how you do it?
How you cry like that?
[slurping]
[chuckles softly]
[chuckling]
[drumming hands on table]
[cackles]
[sniffs]
[crickets chirping]
You see any?
Well, you stopped
holding your breath.
Fuck!
I honestly don't know
how I do it.
I just sort of start crying,
and I can't stop
until I stop recording.
Fucking get this bitch. [grunts]
-[panting]
-[Balthazar] Huh?
Uh...
You gonna hurt somebody?
Solomon?
[muffled] Okay. Let's go.
Huh?
[music playing over speakers]
[door opens]
[electronic doorbell rings]
[Taylor] Solomon.
The fuck are you doing?
Solomon, I see you.
-[whispers] Solomon.
-[Taylor] Solomon.
Solomon, you're not supposed
to be on the premises.
-[Solomon gags]
-What are you doing?
You're freaking me out.
I see you.
[groans]
[Taylor] Solomon?
Solomon, please.
Please, please, please,
don't do anything. I'm sorry.
[Solomon]
Why? Why? Taylor!
[sobbing] Why?
[crying] I just wanted
to be your friend.
-[Taylor] Goddammit, Solomon.
-[shouts]
[Taylor]
You scared the shit out of me.
What the fuck was that?
Well, I just wanted you
to know how you made me feel.
God. You are so fucking weird.
And I wanted to introduce you
to my new friend. [chuckles]
And he came all the way from
New York City to visit me.
Why? So you could dress him up
as Jimmy Phantasm
and suck his dick?
-No.
-[Taylor] Huh?
-Go, go, go, go!
-[Solomon] Stop it!
Stop that, Taylor!
Are you a little pervert
for cartoons, too?
No. No, we are friends.
Hey, tell her--
tell her we're friends.
Huh?
Yeah. We're friends. Yeah.
See, see, I have friends.
-I'm not a fucking incel.
-Yeah, that's right.
Incels don't fuck each other
like you and
butt boy over here.
What? No, we don't--
He's not butt boy,
his name's Balthy.
Sounds like
a butt boy name to me.
I just wanted you to know
that I have a friend.
Fine.
Now leave
or I'll call the cops.
Okay.
[door opens]
[electronic doorbell rings]
[scoffs]
You see her face?
Fuck me.
She fucking felt it, man.
I know she did.
Felt what?
Well, that I'm a person.
You didn't want to shoot her?
[Solomon] Who, Taylor?
Nah, man.
I mean, she's a fucking bitch,
but shoot her?
No way.
[car door closes]
You getting in?
You want to see
where I was going to do it?
My school shooting?
I can show you.
♪ ♪
[whispers] Come on.
Come on.
[whispers] Get down.
This is it, Balthy.
My shooting spot.
I practiced picking off
all the kiddies and teachers.
Picking them off.
One at a time. Mm-hmm.
You try.
♪ ♪
Like this guy?
I could shoot this guy.
Look.
I could shoot him
in the fucking face.
Want me to do it?
[Solomon] Okay.
Show's over.
I can't play this anymore.
Play what?
I'm not this thing.
I'm not. You understand?
Enough is enough.
You know?
What about the maps
you showed me?
I wasn't going to do anything.
They're just stupid
fucking drawings.
If I call someone, can you
at least pretend I stopped you
from doing a shooting?
[dial tone ringing]
[Eleanor] The only reason
I picked up the phone
is to tell you
to stop texting me.
Do you understand?
-Tell me you understand.
-Hey, I--
Hey, look, it's me, Solomon.
I'm with Balthy here,
Balthazar,
and, well, he stopped me
from doing a shooting.
I'm doing no more shootings
any time.
[Eleanor]
I don't know who you are
or how much that freak
paid you to say this,
but you should know
that that freak
likes to make out with people
to videos of school shootings.
Now tell him to stop
calling me, stop texting me.
And if he ever approaches me
at school, ever again,
I will have my mom get
a fucking restraining order
on him.
[cell phone beeps]
You tried to make out with her
to the Arkansas footage
I sent you?
[scoffs]
I didn't even watch that shit.
What's that?
Xanax.
Xanax?
Look. I'm sorry, Balthy. I f--
I know I fucked up.
And you came all--
you came all this way.
I don't have any friends.
What's that?
It's 2C-B.
It's just been in my wallet.
I don't know how long.
Never had anyone
to do it with.
If we do that,
can we go shooting again?
[Solomon chuckles]
You know what?
You might be
the first person I've met
who's weirder than me.
[chuckles]
♪ ♪
Solomon and Balthy.
[muffled gunshots]
[gunshots cracking]
Oh, I think he wants the pistol!
[muffled gunshots]
[laughing]
What?
[continues laughing]
What's so funny, Solomon?
-No! Don't!
-Don't fucking laugh at me.
[Solomon screaming, whimpering]
Don't you fucking
laugh at me, Solomon!
[Solomon gasping]
[laughing]
[Hakeem] What message
are we sending our children
about their future?
About this country's future?
When every day they're afraid
to go to school
because they may not
come out alive?
If this isn't the country
you recognize,
if this isn't the country
you want to recognize,
donate to Hakeem Atkins
for Senate.
I got you.
[laughing quietly]
[cell phone beeps]
[AI Nicole]
Donate to Hakeem
and fuck my creampie pussy.
I want to lick
the shit off your dick
after you donate to Hakeem.
Did you really come up
with all those things
she's saying?
[AI Nicole] Finger me.
Yes.
[Solomon] You remember
that picture I sent you
of my dick?
Can't go wrong, right?
Like your dad?
[giggles]
[AI Nicole] Creampie pussy.
[Balthazar laughing]
Creampie pussy.
Oh, shit. Oh! Fuck.
♪ ♪
Let's go!
[engine rumbling]
[Balthazar giggling]
Thrush.
[rock music playing]
[people cheering]
[man singing indistinctly]
Look at this.
My son, the salesman,
can't go wrong.
-Right, buddy?
-[Solomon] That's right.
Let's go.
[man] ♪ 'Cause I'm running
From the law ♪
That's Supes's girl.
You remember Supes, right?
Yeah.
What'll you have to drink, Sol?
On the old man.
Whatever you're having, Dad.
[man]
♪ Gotta see my mind blown ♪
Oh. I'm sorry. This is Balthy.
He's from New York.
Balthy, what kind of name
is Balthy, huh?
It's French.
It's a man's name.
[chuckles]
You guys, uh,
smoke some wacky tobacky
on the way over here, huh?
Is that what it is?
Watch it, kid.
[Supes] Yeah. Come on, Frenchie,
come over here. Get you a seat.
[music playing over speakers]
Now, look at that,
family business.
-Yeah.
-I bet that 2500's
burning a hole
in your pocket as we speak.
Ah. Yeah, well, I need to pay
rent on Grandma's trailer.
No, no.
In this business, you have got
to take what you made
and invest it.
That's the only way
to make more.
-Basic principles of capitalism.
-[Supes snorting]
Of America.
-You understand?
-Yeah.
No, I don't.
I don't understand.
[laughs] Well, that's okay.
We are inviting you to invest,
inviting you into distribution.
Money that makes money.
-Yeah. Fuck yeah, huh?
-Oh.
What's this?
What's your deal, man?
He autistic?
He looks autistic.
So you get your 25 on what,
Monday, right?
Instead, you sign that sales
slip over to me right now.
On Wednesday,
you get four grand.
Four grand?
I just give you my slip.
I don't have to sell anything?
Shit. You think Supes and me
still bust our hump going door
to door to unload this crap?
Hell fucking no.
You got that slip?
No, I left it at home.
Huh.
Hell, you know what?
Why don't he just bring it
'round the conference tomorrow?
How about that?
-There's an idea.
-Right?
What do you say, kid?
A sale like this,
we have to put you on stage.
[Supes] Of course, man.
That's Thrush legendary shit
right there.
Hey, hey, hey, you know what?
Stage right there.
Get up on it.
Give us a taste.
-Right now?
-You bet your ass, man.
Yeah, man!
Get up on that goddamn stage.
-Show us how it's done.
-Come on.
Suffering builds winning.
-[Beaver] Hey, hey, hey!
-[Supes] That's my fucking line.
You used my goddamn line, man?
Can't go wrong with big Beav
or little Beav.
Why don't you quit
making assumptions, Kate.
-Yeah, Kate.
-Check him out for yourself.
Yeah. Why don't you, uh,
why don't you give
little Beav a tug?
Why don'tcha--
Do it!
[laughs] I'm just kidding.
I'm just fucking with you,
sweetheart.
I'll do it.
Oh, Katy, he ain't--
-[Supes] Whoa!
-[yelping] Dad!
He's not little at all.
[all laugh]
-Hell yeah.
-Yeah.
[laughing]
-Okay.
-Laughing boy loves it.
Yeah, man.
Laughing boy does love it.
[laughing squeakily]
So listen.
Four grand could pay
a lot of rent
on that cunt's
oversized outhouse.
Can you not call her that,
please, Dad?
-[electric guitar stumming]
-You're right. He's right.
She and I have had our
-differences over the years--
-[singer speaking indistinctly]
[Beaver] ...but I get that
she means a lot to you.
-And, hey, I respect that.
-[rock music playing]
This is a privileged position
we're offering you here, Solly.
-[Supes] Distribution.
-I know.
This is me
being a good father to you.
Guiding you, son.
I got you.
[Balthazar] It's a grift.
[man singing indistinctly]
What? What'd you say?
Um, it's a grift.
He's making you care
about something
so he can take your money.
Solly, who the fuck is this kid?
-Shut the fuck up.
-It's a grifty grifty.
Shut the fuck up, Balthy.
You believe I met
this little freak online?
And then he shows up
out of nowhere
and starts following me around
like a retarded puppy.
Listen, Balthazar,
why don't you go wait outside
in the car
and let the real men talk?
Yeah. You tell him, son.
I didn't just show up.
I came here to stop you
from shooting up a school.
What'd he say? What'd you say?
I came here to stop him
from shooting up a school.
Hey, Balthy. Balthy, shut up!
Shut the fuck up! What school?
-He showed me his plans.
-Shut up!
-You said you were gonna do it.
-[Solomon] Know what?
-Like in Arkansas City.
-What--
What did you just say
about Arkansas City?
[Beaver] Okay.
What did you say
about Arkansas City?
He sent me videos
of kids getting shot.
In Arkansas City?
[Beaver] I told you
he had people there.
Fucking fuck off, Beaver.
I said shut the fuck up.
He's joking. He's high.
So you think this is funny, huh?
Is that what you guys
both think?
This is fucking funny, huh?
It's death. Real death.
[Katy shrieks]
You son of a bitch.
-You think this is funny, huh?
-[Balthazar groaning]
-[Katy shrieks]
-[Supes] Huh?
-What?
-Hey, hey!
-Are you planning something?
-No! I'm not.
-I'm not, I was trolling him.
Oh, so you think
this is funny, huh?
Do you know what a. 223 did
to my little cousin's face?
Huh? Okay, I'll show you.
How about that?
I'll take
this fucking dart, huh,
and I'll shove it
through your goddamn ear.
-You stupid son of a bitch!
-Dad!
I'll shove this dart through
your goddamn fucking ear.
-How about that?
-[woman] Hey, hey!
Break this shit up right now.
Take it outside.
Get the fuck out of here.
Go.
Take your loser kid
and you fuck off
before I gut him.
-We're about to close.
-Get him out!
-Get out of here, Sol.
-[woman] Go now!
Go.
-[woman] Now!
-[Solomon shouts indistinctly]
[Beaver] Hey! Sol, Sol.
Hold up, hold up.
[sighs]
Hey, listen, man.
Uh...
about that deal, distribution?
You in?
Gotta pay rent.
Dad, me and Grandma
are gonna get kicked out.
Oh for Christ's sake, Solomon,
are you a man or what?
Are you my son or not?
Now I need the money
before you said I'd get it.
Okay.
That's fine.
I get it. I'll get it Wednesday.
You will?
Yeah. Yeah. Right.
I'm sorry, Dad.
You fucking embarrass me
like that.
Dad, I can't.
-You--
-I can't.
-Give me that money!
-Dad, I can't.
-[Solomon] No!
-[Beaver] Stand up!
-[Solomon sniffling]
[Beaver] Oh, man.
'Course you're going to whine.
Don't be showing up
at that conference
begging me to be your daddy.
You make me sick, Solomon.
[spits]
[indistinct chatter]
Where am I sleeping?
On the floor?
Waste of my time.
You're a waste of time, Solomon.
[gun cocks]
[no audible dialogue]
♪ ♪
Are you ready for war?
[whispers] Balthazar.
Aren't you going to tell me
where we're going?
The source.
Going to the source.
I get what I want.
You get what you want.
♪ ♪
What is this?
Everyone always said
I was this thing.
I've tried to be that thing.
I've tried not to be that thing.
But I guess I am what I am.
You just let me get my dad.
And after that, take me out.
[cocks gun]
Make sure my grandma gets
the money from that sale.
[sighs]
It's not even a school.
No one's going to care.
You ready to be a hero,
Balthazar?
Hey.
♪ ♪
-[Solomon] Let's go.
-[trunk shuts]
Come on, Balthazar.
♪ ♪
Balthy, come on.
Solomon.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
What the hell are you doing?
You crazy?
-Okay.
-[gun clicks]
Please!
Okay. Solly. Hey.
Is this about last night?
[exhales]
I fell off the wagon.
And I will admit that I got
a little out of hand.
I am a work in progress,
Solomon.
Okay?
Those the guns I got you
for your birthday?
You got them to me to hide.
Okay.
You know what? I fucked up.
And [stammers] I've been
fucking up for a long time.
I would like to try to change.
I'm trying to change for us.
Don't do anything you'll regret.
I'm your daddy.
I love you.
Stop!
[Beaver] Okay.
Okay.
Balthy, he's my dad.
Balthy, he's my dad!
Put it down!
[door opens]
[door closes]
Balthy...
Could you...
Will you stay
just one more night?
-[police siren on TV]
-Hey, what's the matter, Solly?
You okay?
Hey, Sol?
[crying]
They have taxis here,
don't they?
[continues crying]
[Solomon] Balthy.
Please.
Please just be my friend.
Stop.
I can't believe I thought
you were a school shooter.
Look at you.
Stop crying. It's disgusting.
You hate me,
don't you?
You think I'm pathetic?
Yes, I do. Yes. Yes, yes, yes.
You're just a poor, dumb loser.
[Solomon crying]
I'm gonna rip this up if you
don't stop crying, Solomon.
No! No.
[grunts]
[Balthazar]
What are you doing?
Stop it!
[gun fires]
[high-pitched ringing]
[muffled speech]
[muffled groans]
[Elaine screams]
[Solomon, muffled] Grandma!
[groans]
[sobs]
[police siren wailing on TV]
[Solomon] What did you do?
It's not my fault.
[police siren
continues wailing on TV]
[dog barking]
[gun firing]
[alarm blaring]
[Solomon] Balthazar.
Balthazar!
[shrieks]
This is what you wanted, right?
Here I am.
[police siren wailing
in distance]
[car alarm stops]
[Myron] What the fuck's
going on, Solly?
Shut the fuck up, Myron!
[Myron] shit!
[Solomon] Shut the fuck up.
[moans]
[gun fires]
[police siren continues wailing
in distance]
♪ ♪
[dial tone ringing]
[Antony] Hi. You've reached
the voicemail of life coach
and personal
chief of staff Antony Kelly.
Please leave your name
and number
and I'll get back
to you ASAP.
And please, always remember,
be kind.
Antony, it's me.
Um, I'm in Arlington, Texas.
Will you contact
Dad's legal team?
[no audible dialogue]
[police siren continues wailing]
So, he just went crazy?
I just wanted to be his friend.
I came here to stop him
from shooting up a school.
He showed me his plans
like in Arkansas City.
♪ ♪
♪ Yo, Jimmy was
Your average teen ♪
♪ A brainiac whiz ♪
♪ Who invented a machine
To catch ghosts ♪
♪ Track them with EVP ♪
♪ And zap them
With a subatomic laser beam ♪
♪ One night
He was out ghost hunting ♪
♪ But Jimmy accidentally hit
The wrong button ♪
♪ He tried to make it stop
But it was too late ♪
♪ Jimmy's DNA
Had started to mutate ♪
♪ When Jimmy got zapped
The ghost did too ♪
♪ They both got trapped
And their souls got fused ♪
♪ His eyes turned green
And his hair turned blue ♪
♪ But he can do things
That a ghost can do ♪
♪ Float through the walls of
His high school classroom ♪
♪ Blast other ghosts
With his ectoplasm ♪
♪ Jimmy's got powers
That no one has ♪
♪ Half ghost, half kid
That's Jimmy Phantasm ♪
[woman] Balthazar?
Are you sure you're okay, honey?
Yeah.
I'm fine.
I saw you're speaking
at the convention tomorrow.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm trying to get my story out.
Well, I'll be there.
Balthazar, this is our host,
Armand Lewis.
Balthazar. Hello.
Uh, I hear you like to go
by Balthy.
-Uh, Balthazar, please.
-Got it.
Uh, we good to go?
Okay. So they're gonna roll,
and I'm just gonna ask you
a few questions.
That sound all right with you?
Mm-hmm. One sec, please.
[woman] Okay.
In five, four, three...
[Armand] Balthazar Malone.
Let's get right to it.
Some say you're a hero.
Some say murderer.
Others say
you're just another victim
in a hopeless epidemic that
only children in America face.
So, in your own words,
Balthazar.
How do you see yourself?
♪ ♪
[Armand on TV]
It's okay. Take your time.
I mean, there's one test that
damn near everybody's got it.
Put your hand up
for me like this.
Okay. There you go. Right there.
This and this. Right, Supes?
[Balthazar speaks indistinctly,
sighs on TV]
We...
are fighting...
for our--
["Vendetta" by Iceage playing]
♪ Tired of misbehaving ♪
♪ Call those shots
Upon those pricks ♪
♪ We're fixing to skin 'em ♪
♪ Every trickster knows ♪
♪ There's an onslaught ♪
♪ And every city's
Flooded with cocaine ♪
♪ Fuck a broken backbone ♪
♪ You're wasted
On this site ♪
♪ Did you earn
To belong here? ♪
♪ This ain't no place
For a sightseer ♪
♪ Looking for promotion ♪
♪ Mitigate a problem ♪
♪ Then dump it in the ocean ♪
♪ Nurse onto these grudges
For my sake ♪
♪ Here grievances run
Within the family ♪
♪ Meddle into interest ♪
♪ Where business
You got none ♪
♪ See yourself
Deemed a stressor ♪
♪ Every man is
Someone's successor ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Beating on an iron door ♪
♪ You're looking
Like an animal ♪
♪ Cock the hammer
Tuck it in ♪
♪ We keep it close
We keep with kin ♪
♪ Vendetta ♪
♪ I'ma gonna getcha ♪
[vocalizing]
♪ The plates
From which we eat from ♪
♪ Life in the trenches
Of a Ponzi scheme to come ♪
♪ Cutthroat contract ♪
♪ Jackleg wildflower ♪
♪ A nettle
In the nursery humdrum ♪
♪ Hellbent chasing paper ♪
♪ Upon a mile of road ♪
♪ Buyer, seller
Seller and buyer ♪
♪ How much are you
Taking for hire? ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Beating on an iron door ♪
♪ You're looking
Like an animal ♪
♪ Cock the hammer
Tuck it in ♪
♪ We keep it close
We keep with kin ♪
♪ Vendetta ♪
♪ I'ma gonna getcha ♪
[vocalizing]